Look‚ I was gonna go easy on you
and not to hurt your feelings
But I am only going to
get this one chance
Something′s wrong‚ I can feel it (Six
minutes‚ Slim Shady‚ You are on)
Just a feeling I have got‚ like
something′s about to happen‚
but I don′t know what
If that means‚ what I think it means‚
We are in trouble‚ big trouble
And if he is as bananas as you say‚
I am not taking any chances
You were just what the doctor ordered
I am beginning to feel like
a Rap God‚ Rap God
All my people from the front
to the back nod‚ back nod
Now who thinks their arms are long
enough to slap box‚ slap box?
They said I rap like a robot‚
so call me Rapbot
But for me to rap like a computer
must be in my genes
I got a laptop in my back pocket
My pen′ll go off when I half cock it
Got a fat knot from that rap profit
Made a living and a killing off it
Ever since Bill Clinton
was still in office
With Monica Lewinsky feeling
on his nut sack
I am an MC still as honest
But as rude and indecent as
all hell syllables‚ killaholic
(Kill them all with)
This slickety‚ gibbedy‚
hibbedy hip hop
You don′t really wanna get into a pissing
match with this rappidy rap
Packing a Mac in the back of the Ac‚
pack backpack rap‚ yep‚ yackidy yac
The exact same time I attempt
these lyrical acrobat stunts
while I am practicing
That I will still be able to
break a motherfuckin table
Over the back of a couple of faggots
and crack it in half
Only realized it was ironic I was signed
to Aftermath after the fact
How could I not blow? All I do is drop
F bombs‚ feel my wrath of attack
Rappers are having a rough time
period‚ here′s a Maxipad
It is actually disastrously bad
For the wack while I am masterfully
constructing this masterpiece as
I am beginning to feel like
a Rap God‚ Rap God
All my people from the front
to the back nod‚ back nod
Now who thinks their arms are long
enough to slap box‚ slap box?
Let me show you maintaining this
shit ain′t that hard‚ that hard
Everybody want the key and the secret
to rap immortality like I have got
Well‚ to be truthful the blueprint′s
simply rage and youthful exuberance
Everybody loves to root for a nuisance
Hit the earth like an asteroid‚ did nothing
but shoot for the moon since
MC′s get taken to school
with this music
Cause I use it as a vehicle
to bust a rhyme
Now I lead a new school
full of students
Me? I am a product of Rakim‚
Lakim Shabazz‚ 2Pac N
W.A‚ Cube‚ hey‚ Doc‚ Ren‚ Yella‚
Eazy‚ thank you‚ they got Slim
Inspired enough to one day grow up‚
blow up and be in a position
To met Run DMC and induct them
into the motherfuckin Rock n′
Roll Hall of Fame
Even though I walk in the church
and burst in a ball of flames
Only Hall of Fame I be inducted
in is the alcohol of fame
On the wall of shame
You fags think It is all a game
′til I walk a flock of flames
Off of planking‚ tell me what in
the fuck are you thinking?
Little gay looking boy
So gay I can barely say it with
a straight face looking boy
You witnessing a massacre
Like you watching a church gathering
take place looking boy
Oy vey‚ that boy′s gay‚ that′s
all they say looking boy
You get a thumbs up‚ pat on the back
And a way to go from your label
everyday looking boy
Hey‚ looking boy‚ what
you say looking boy?
I got a hell yeah from Dre looking boy
I am work for everything I have
Never ask nobody for shit‚ get
outta my face looking boy
Basically boy You are never
gonna be capable
To keep up with the same
pace looking boy
′Cause I am beginning to feel
like a Rap God‚ Rap God
All my people from the front
to the back nod‚ back nod
The way I am racing around the
track‚ call me Nascar‚ Nascar
Dale Earnhardt of the trailer
park‚ the White Trash God
Kneel before General Zod this planet′s
Krypton‚ no Asgard‚ Asgard
So you be Thor and I will be Odin‚
you rodent‚ I am omnipotent
Let off then I am reloading immediately
with these bombs I am totin′
And I should not be woken
I am the walking dead‚ but I am just
a talking head‚ a zombie floating
But I got your mom deep throating
I am out my ramen noodle‚ we have
nothing in common‚ poodle
I am a doberman‚ pinch yourself in
the arm and pay homage‚ pupil
It is me‚ my honesty′s brutal
But It is honestly futile if I don′t
utilize what I do though
For good at least once in a while
So I wanna make sure somewhere
in this chicken scratch
I scribble and doodle
Enough rhymes to maybe to
try and help get some people
through tough times
But I gotta keep a few punchlines just
in case cause even you unsigned
Rappers are hungry looking at
me like It is lunchtime
I know there was a time where once I
Was king of the underground‚
but I still rap like I am
on my Pharoahe Monch grind
So I crunch rhymes‚ but sometimes
when you combine
Appeal with the skin color of mine
You get too big and here
they come trying to
Censor you like that one line
I said on I am Back from
the Marshall Mathers LP
One where I tried to say I take
seven kids from Columbine
Put them all in a line‚ add an
AK 47‚ a revolver and a nine
See if I get away with it now that I
ain′t as big as I was‚ but I have
Morphed into an immortal coming
through the portal
You are stuck in a time
warp from 2004 though
And I don′t know what the
fuck that you rhyme for
You are pointless as Rapunzel
with fucking cornrows
You are like normal‚ fuck being normal
And I just bought a new
Raygun from the future
To just come and shoot ya like
when Fabolous made Ray J mad
′Cause Fab said he looked like
a fag at Maywhether′s pad
Singin′ to a man while
they played piano
Man‚ oh man‚ that was a 24 7 special
on the cable channel
So Ray J went straight to the radio
station the very next day
Hey‚ Fab‚ I am kill you
Lyrics coming at you at supersonic
speed‚ (JJ Fad)
Uh‚ sama lamaa duma lamaa you
assuming I am a human
What I gotta do to get it through
to you I am superhuman
Innovative and I am made of rubber
So that anything you saying ricocheting
off of me and it′ll glue to you
I am never stating‚ more than
never demonstrating
How to give a motherfuckin audience
a feeling like It is levitating
Never fading‚ and I know that the
haters are forever waiting
For the day that they can say I fell
off‚ They had be celebrating
Cause I know the way to
get them motivated
I make elevating music‚ you
make elevator music
Oh‚ He is too mainstream
Well‚ that′s what they do when they
get jealous‚ they confuse it
It is not hip hop‚ It is pop‚ cause
I found a hella way to fuse it
With rock‚ shock rap with Doc
Throw on Lose Yourself
and make them lose it
I don′t know how to make
songs like that
I don′t know what words to use
Let me know when it occurs to you
While I am ripping any one of
these verses diverse as you
It is curtains‚ I am inadvertently
hurtin′ you
How many verses I gotta murder to
Prove that if You are half
as nice at songs you can sacrifice
virgins too uh!
School flunkie‚ pill junky
But look at the accolades
the skills brung me
Full of myself‚ but still hungry
I bully myself cause I make me
do what I put my mind to
And I am a million leagues above you‚
ill when I speak in tongues
But It is still tongue
in chek‚ fuck you
I am drunk so Satan take the fucking
whel‚ I am asleep in the front seat
Bumping Heavy D and the Boys‚
still chunky‚ but funky
But in my head there′s something I
can feel tugging and struggling
Angels fight with devils‚ here′s
what they want from me
They asking me to eliminate
some of the women hate
But if you take into consideration
the bitter hatred that I had
Then you may be a little patient and
more sympathetic to the situation
And understand the discrimination
But fuck it‚ life′s handing you
lemons‚ make lemonade then
But if I can′t batter the women
how the fuck am I supposed
to bake them a cake then?
Don′t mistake it for Satan
It is a fatal mistake if you
think I need to be overseas
And take a vacation to trip a broad
And make her fall on her face
and don′t be a retard
Be a king? Think not‚ why be a
king when you can be a God?
www.RentAnAdviser.com