Is this the real life?
Is this just fantasy?
Caught in a landslide
No escape from reality
Open your eyes
Look up to the skies and see
I am just a poor boy‚
I need no sympathy
Because I am easy come‚ easy go
A little high‚ little low
Anyway the wind blows‚ doesn′t
really matter to me‚ to me
Mama‚ just killed a man
Put a gun against his head
Pulled my trigger‚ now He is dead
Mama‚ life had just begun
But now I have gone and
thrown it all away
Mama‚ oo
Didn′t mean to make you cry
If I am not back again
this time tomorrow
Carry on‚ carry on‚ as if
nothing really matters
Too late‚ my time has come
Sends shivers down my spine
Body′s aching all the time
Goodbye everybody I have got to go
Gotta leave you all behind
and face the truth
Mama‚ oo (anyway the wind blows)
I don′t want to die
I sometimes wish I had never
been born at all
I see a little silhouetto of a man
Scaramouch‚ scaramouch will
you do the fandango
Thunderbolt and lightning
very very frightening me
Gallileo‚ Gallileo
Gallileo Figaro magnifico
But I am just a poor boy
and nobody loves me
He is just a poor boy
from a poor family
Spare him his life from
this monstrosity
Easy come easy go will you let me go
Bismillah! No we will not
let you go let him go
Bismillah! We will not
let you go let me go
Will not let you go let me go (never)
Never let you go let me go
Never let me go oo
No‚ no‚ no‚ no‚ no‚ no‚ no
Oh mama mia‚ mama mia‚
mama mia let me go
Beelzebub has a devil put aside for me
For me
So you think you can stop
me and spit in my eye
So you think you can love
me and leave me to die
Oh baby can′t do this to me baby
Just gotta get out just gotta
get right outta here
Ooh yeah‚ ooh yeah
Nothing really matters
Anyone can see
Nothing really matters nothing
really matters to me
Anyway the wind blows
www.RentAnAdviser.com