Day and night (what‚ what)
I toss and turn‚ I keep stressing
my mind‚ mind (what‚ what)
I look for peace but see I
don′t attain (what‚ what)
What I need for keeps this
silly game we play‚ play
Now look at this (what‚ what)
Madness to magnet keeps attracting
me‚ me (what‚ what)
I try to run but see I am not
that fast (what‚ what)
I think I am first but surely
finish last‚ last
′cause day and night
The lonely stoner seems to
free his mind at night
He is all alone through
the day and night
The lonely loner seems to free his
mind at night (at‚ at‚ at night)
Day and night
The lonely stoner seems to
free his mind at night
He is all alone‚ some things will
never change (never change)
The lonely loner seems to free his
mind at night (at‚ at‚ at night)
The pain is deep (what‚ what)
A silent sleeper you won′t hear
a peep‚ peep (what‚ what)
The girl he wants don′t
seem to want him too
It seems the feelings that she
had are through‚ through
′cause day and night
The lonely stoner seems to
free his mind at night
He is all alone through
the day and night
The lonely loner seems to free his
mind at night (at‚ at‚ at night)
Day and night
The lonely stoner seems to
free his mind at night
He is all alone‚ some things will
never change (never change)
The lonely loner seems to free his
mind at night (at‚ at‚ at night)
Day and night
The lonely stoner seems to
free his mind at night
He is all alone‚ some things will
never change (never change)
The lonely loner seems to free his
mind at night (at‚ at‚ at night)
www.RentAnAdviser.com