Standing in line
To see the show tonight
And there′s a light on
Heavy glow
By the way I tried to say
I had be there‚ waiting for
Dani the girl
Is singing songs to me
Beneath the marquee‚ overload
Steak knife card shark
Con job boot cut
Skin that flick
She is such a little DJ
Get there quick
By street but not the freeway
Turn that trick
To make a little leeway
Beat that nic
But not the way that we play
Dog town blood bath
Rib cage soft tail
Standing in line
To see the show tonight
And there′s a light on
Heavy glow
By the way I tried to say
I had be there‚ waiting for
Black jack dope dick
Pawn shop quick pick
Kiss that dyke
I know you want to hold one
Not on strike
But I am about to bowl one
Bite that mic
I know you never stole one
Girls that like
A story‚ so I told one
Song bird‚ main line
Cash back‚ hard top
Standing in line to
See the show tonight
And there′s a light on
Heavy glow
By the way I tried to say
I had be there waiting for
Dani the girl is
Singing songs to me
Beneath the marquee
Oversold
By the way I tried to say
I had be there waiting for
Ooh‚ ah‚ guess you never meant it
Ooh‚ ah
Standing in line to
See the show tonight
And there′s a light on
Heavy glow
By the way I tried to say
I had be there waiting for
Dani the girl
Is singing songs to me
Beneath the marquee
Of her soul
By the way I tried to say
I know you
From before
Standing in line to
See the show tonight
And there′s a light on
Heavy glow
By the way I tried to say
I had be there waiting for
www.RentAnAdviser.com