It is BEEN A LONG DAY WITHOUT
YOU‚ MY FRIEND
AND I will TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
WE′VE COME A LONG WAY
FROM WHERE WE BEGAN
OH‚ I will TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
[ Rapping ] DAMN‚ WHO KNEW
ALL THE PLANES WE FLEW
GOOD THINGS WE BEEN THROUGH
THAT I had BE STANDING RIGHT HERE
TALKING TO YOU ′BOUT ANOTHER PATH
I KNOW WE LOVED TO HIT
THE ROAD AND LAUGH
BUT SOMETHING TOLD ME THAT
IT WOULDN′T LAST
HAD TO SWITCH UP‚ LOOK
AT THINGS DIFFERENT
SEE THE BIGGER PICTURE
THOSE WERE THE DAYS‚ HARD
WORK FOREVER PAYS
NOW I SEE YOU IN A BETTER PLACE
SEE YOU IN A BETTER PLACE
UNH
HOW COULD WE NOT TALK ABOUT FAMILY
WHEN FAMILY′S ALL THAT WE GOT?
EVERYTHING I WENT THROUGH
YOU WERE STANDING THERE BY MY SIDE
AND NOW YOU GON′ BE WITH
ME FOR THE LAST RIDE
It is BEEN A LONG DAY WITHOUT
YOU‚ MY FRIEND
AND I will TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
I will SEE YOU AGAIN
WE′VE COME A LONG WAY
CAME A LONG WAY
FROM WHERE WE BEGAN
OH‚ I will TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
LET ME TELL YOU
WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
OH‚ OH‚ OH‚ OH
OH‚ OH‚ OH‚ OH OH OH OH
OOH OOH OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH
OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH OOH OOH
OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH OOH
[ Rapping ] FIRST‚ YOU
BOTH GO OUT YOUR WAY
AND THE VIBE IS FEELING STRONG
AND WHAT′S SMALL TURNED
TO A FRIENDSHIP
A FRIENDSHIP TURNED TO A BOND
AND THAT BOND WILL NEVER BE BROKEN
THE LOVE WILL NEVER GET LOST
AND THE LOVE WILL NEVER GET LOST
AND WHEN BROTHERHOOD COME FIRST
THEN THE LINE WILL NEVER BE CROSSED
ESTABLISHED IT ON OUR OWN
WHEN THAT LINE HAD TO BE DRAWN
AND THAT LINE IS WHAT WE REACHED
SO REMEMBER ME WHEN I am GONE
REMEMBER ME WHEN I am GONE
HOW COULD WE NOT TALK ABOUT FAMILY
WHEN FAMILY′S ALL THAT WE GOT?
EVERYTHING I WENT THROUGH
YOU WERE STANDING THERE BY MY SIDE
AND NOW YOU GON′ BE WITH
ME FOR THE LAST RIDE
LET THE LIGHT GUIDE YOUR WAY
YEAH
HOLD EVERY MEMORY AS YOU GO
AND EVERY ROAD YOU TAKE
WILL ALWAYS LEAD YOU HOME
HOME
It is BEEN A LONG DAY WITHOUT
YOU‚ MY FRIEND
AND I will TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
WE′VE COME A LONG WAY
FROM WHERE WE BEGAN
OH‚ I will TELL YOU ALL ABOUT
IT WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
OH‚ OH‚ OH‚ OH
OH‚ OH‚ OH‚ OH OH OH OH
OOH OOH OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH
OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH OOH OOH
OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH OOH
WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN
SEE YOU AGAIN
OH‚ OH‚ OH‚ OH
OH‚ OH‚ OH‚ OH OH OH
OOH OOH OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH
OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH OOH OOH
OOH OOH‚ OOH OOH OOH
WHEN I SEE YOU AGAIN