You were my sun‚ you were my earth
But you didn′t know all the
ways I loved you‚ no
So you took a chance‚ made other plans
But I bet you didn′t think that they
would come crashing down‚ no
You don′t have to say‚ what you did
I already know‚ I found out from him
Now there′s just no chance
With you and me
There′ll never be
Don′t it make you sad about it?
You told me you love me
Why did you leave me all alone
Now you tell me you need me
When you call me on the phone
Girl I refuse
You must have me confused
with some other guy
The bridges were burned
Now It is your turn‚ to cry
Cry me a river
You know that they say somethings
are better left unsaid
It wasn′t like you only talked to him
And you know it
(Don′t act like you don′t know it)
All of these things people told me
Keep messing with my head
should have picked honesty
Then you may not have thought it
You don′t have to say‚ what you did
I already know‚ I found out from him
Now there′s just no chance
With you and me
There′ll never be
Don′t it make you sad about it?
You told me you love me
Why did you leave me all alone
Now you tell me you need me
When you call me on the phone
Girl I refuse
You must have me confused
with some other guy
The bridges were burned
Now It is your turn‚ to cry
Cry me a river (Go on and just)
Cry me a river (Baby go on and just)
Cry me a river
Oh!
The damage is done‚ so
I guess I be leaving
Oh!
The damage is done‚ so
I guess I be leaving
Oh!
The damage is done‚ so
I guess I be leaving
Oh!
The damage is done‚ so
I guess I be leaving
You don′t have to say‚ what you did
I already know‚ I found out from him
Now there′s just no chance
With you and me
There′ll never be
Don′t it make you sad about it?
Cry me a river (Go on and just)
Cry me a river (Baby go on and just)
Cry me a river (You can
go on and just)
Cry me a river
Cry me a river (Baby go on and just)
Cry me a river (Go on and just)
Cry me a river (Oh baby cry)
Cry me a river (I don′t
wanna cry no more)
Cry me a river
Cry me a river (Cry me‚ cry me)
www.RentAnAdviser.com