Psychic spies from China
Try to steal your mind′s elation
And little girls from Sweden
Dreams of silver screen quotation
And if you want these kind of dreams
It is Californication
It is the edge of the world
And all of western civilization
The sun may rise in the East
At least it settles in
the final location
It is understood that Hollywood
Sells Californication
Pay your surgeon very well
To break the spell of aging
Celebrity skin is this your chin
Or is that war your waging
First born unicorn
Hard core soft porn
Dream of Californication
Marry me girl be my fairy to the world
Be my very own constellation
A teenage bride with a baby inside
Getting high on information
And buy me a star on the boulevard
It is Californication
Space may be the final frontier
But It is made in a Hollywood basement
Cobain can you hear the spheres
Singing songs off station to station
And Alderaan′s not far away
It is Californication
Born and raised by those who praise
Control of population everybody′s
been there and
I don′t mean on vacation
First born unicorn
Hard core soft porn
Dream of Californication
Destruction leads to a very rough road
But it also breeds creation
And earthquakes are to a girl′s guitar
They are just another good vibration
And tidal waves couldn′t
save the world
From Californication
Pay your surgeon very well
To break the spell of aging
Sicker than the rest
There is no test
But this is what You are craving
First born unicorn
Hard core soft porn
Dream of Californication
www.RentAnAdviser.com