By RentAnAdviser.com
I see a red door and I
want it painted black
No colors any more‚ I want
them to turn black
I see the girls walk by‚ dressed
in their summer clothes
I have to turn my head until
my darkness goes
I see a line of cars and They
are all painted black
With flowers and my love
both never to come back
I see people turn their heads
and quickly look away
Like a newborn baby‚ it
just happens every day
I look inside myself and
see my heart is black
I see my red door I must
have it painted black
Maybe then I will fade away and
not have to face the facts
It is not easy facing up when
your whole world is black
No more will my green sea
go turn a deeper blue
I could not foresee this
thing happening to you
If I look hard enough
into the setting sun
My love will laugh with me
before the morning comes
I see a red door and I
want it painted black
No colors any more‚ I want
them to turn black
I see the girls walk by‚ dressed
in their summer clothes
I have to turn my head until
my darkness goes
Hmm‚ hmm‚ hmm
I wanna see it painted‚ painted black
Black as night‚ black as coal
I wanna see the sun blotted
out from the sky
I wanna see it painted‚ painted‚
painted‚ painted black
Yeah!
Hmm‚ hmm‚ hmm
By RentAnAdviser.com