By RentAnAdviser.com
Mama Mavis‚ oh
Mama‚ they tried my patience
Obama is gone‚ who is left to save us?
So together we mourn‚ I am
praying for my neighbors
They say the devil′s at work
and Trump is calling favors
You say I am dangerous‚ I
speak for the nameless
I fly with the vultures‚
I be with them bangers
If change don′t come‚ then
the change won′t come
If the bands make ′em dance‚
then the rain gon′ come
(Woo!)
Am I passin′ into the light?
(Am I looking into mercy′s eyes?)
look into your eyes
All the world is out of your hands
(Then ascending into the
dark‚ let me out)
You got to die a little
if you wanna live
Change come to pass
you had best be ready for it
Something I have begun to fear
is about to change it is form
Yeah‚ yeah‚ yeah‚ it
is a shift in time
But I won′t get tired at all
Let me out‚ let me out
Look into my eyes‚ mama‚
tell me what you see
Tell me there′s a chance for me
to make it off the streets
Tell me that I won′t die at
the hands of the police
Promise me I won′t outlive
my nephew and my niece
Promise me my pastor isn′t
lyin′ as he preach
Tell me that they′ll listen if
it is lessons that I teach
Tell me there′s a heaven in the
sky where there is peace
But until then‚ I keep my
piece in arm′s reach
Am I passin′ into the light?
(Am I looking into mercy′s eyes?)
All the world is out of your hands
(Then ascending into the
dark) another night
You got to die a little
if you wanna live
Change coming
you had best be ready for it
Something I have begun to fear
is about to change it is form
Yeah‚ yeah‚ yeah‚ it
is a shift in times
But I won′t get tired at all
Am I passin′ into the light?
(Am I looking into mercy′s eyes?)
All the world is out of your hands
(Then ascending into the
dark) another night
You got to die a little
if you wanna live
Change is coming
you had best be ready
Be ready‚ ready for it
Be ready‚ be ready
(Let me out)
I'll it's don't