Stop!
With your feet on the air
And your head on the ground
Try this trick and spin it
Yeah
Your head will collapse
But there's nothing in it
And you'll ask yourself
Where is my mind?
Wheeere is my mind?...
Way out..
In the water
See it swimmin'
I was swimmin'
in the Caribbean
Animals were hiding
behind the rock
Except the little fish
But they told me, he swears
Tryin' to talk to me, coy koi.
Where is my mind?
Wheeere is my mind?...
Way out..
In the water
see it swimmin'
With your feet on the air
And your head on the ground
Try this trick and spin it
Yeah
Your head will collapse
If there's nothing in it
And you'll ask yourself
Where is my mind?
Wheeere is my mind?...
Way out..
In the water
see it swimmin'
With your feet on the air
And your head on the ground
Try this trick and spin it
Yeah
(You met me at a very
strange time in my life...)