By RentAnAdviser.com
Where is the moment when
we needed the most?
You kick up the leaves‚
and the magic is lost
They tell me your blue
sky′s faded to gray
They tell me your passion′s gone away
And I don′t need no carrying on
Stand in the line just
to hit a new low
You are faking a smile
with the coffee to go
You tell me your life′s
been way off line
You are falling to pieces every time
And I don′t need no carrying on
′Cause you had a bad day
You are taking one down
You sing a sad song just
to turn it around
You say you don′t know
You tell me don′t lie
You work at a smile‚ and
you go for a ride
You had a bad day
The camera don′t lie
You are coming back down‚ and
you really don′t mind
You had a bad day
Well you need a blue sky holiday
The point is they laugh
at what you say
And I don′t need no carrying on
You had a bad day
You are taking one down
You sing a sad song just
to turn it around
You say you don′t know
You tell me don′t lie
You work at a smile‚ and
you go for a ride
You had a bad day
The camera don′t lie
You are coming back down and
you really don′t mind
You had a bad day
Sometimes the system goes on
the blink‚ and the whole
thing it turns out wrong
You might not make it back and
you know that you could
be well‚ oh‚ that strong
And I am not wrong yeah
So where is the passion when
you need it the most?
Oh‚ you and I
You kick up the leaves
and the magic is lost
′Cause you had a bad day
You are taking one down
You sing a sad song just
to turn it around
You say you don′t know
You tell me don′t lie
You work at a smile and
you go for a ride
You had a bad day
You see what you like
And how does it feel one more time?
You had a bad day
had a bad day
By RentAnAdviser.com